Hi guys, it's me again I'm sorry for splitting the video into two
parts because I only have five minutes for each loom video,
so Yeah, about the last hook that I'm talking
about And what is the audio hook, which is,
I think this is the best example. So,
yeah, the avatar swears at the very first second of the video that makes
it, uhm, engaging. Also,
uh, yeah,
that one. So I use, uhm, audio effects,
cause psychologically speaking,
it, uhm, it gains,
uhm, uhm, uhm, attention for the viewers and make them stop scrolling.
So except that, I,
uh, use this format because this is a trending
ad format online.
So I think using it. It's a plus on this one.
Yeah. And then. Except these three
types of hooks. I also think that in an AI vid,
the most important thing to consider first is to have a AI video that
does. Doesn't look AI at all. You know what I mean?
Like, because people nowadays hates AI.
So it's, I think it's a must. And how do I resolve that?
So I resolved that using this ready to use.
Prompts in my desktop, which is they have their own different
types of purpose. Like example,
this one is, I always use this one because this one makes
this type of videos. Which is clips
that doesn't look AI at all.
So you can actually notice which one is there,
which one in here is the AI and which one is the actual b-roll.
Yeah, so that's it. That's the purpose of that prompt.
And then this one is for AI visuals, which is,
um, animated ones. Uh,
not this one specifically,
uh, wait,
wait a minute. Yeah. This one, this.
Types of animation. So it's the most complex one.
It can create a lot of AI visuals, actually.
Then this one is the clinical endoscopic,
which is this one, just gore looking realistic.
Once, and then, uh,
Pixar Animated, which is this one.
Yeah, this one.
No, no, no, no, no. This one,
I mean. Yeah. Pixar Animated videos.
And then, um, Skeleton, which is my favorite of all.
Yeah, this one. So,
the question is, how do I use it,
and how considerate is it,
and how accurate it is, and how efficient it is.
So, I just need to copy it,
put it inside here, copy
it and paste in here then it's my choice if
I have to specify it or I just put the script here,
let's say, uhm, uhm, 40-year-old
man walking on a street.
So, yeah, that's just an example. So I usually have my avatar
provided first, so,
so they just need to make the avatar moving.
So, yeah. The cloud will give
me everything. That I need to prompt it. So I just keep on doing
it. And then it will just consistently give me accurate
scenes and high quality scenes.
And I will just put everything on CapCut,
add some transitions, sound effects. Background music if needed.
And then, yeah, I'm done. I think that's basically it.
Also, about the captions. So I usually rely on,
uhm, client preferences before I do all of it.
So, I think that's basically it.
I don't have much time left and I,
I think I exceeded a lot of time based on your 8 minute,
8 minute time mark so I hope you still consider this,
ah, loom video. And,
yeah, thank you for watching. I hope we can talk a lot more and
I hope I can look forward working with you.
Thank you.